http://www.constructionbidding.com/privacy-policy

561.656.4701support@planhub.comSearch Projects by StateHomeHow It WorksFeatures & BenefitsPricingRequest A DemoFAQsSolutionsGeneral ContractorsSubcontractorsSuppliersPartners & Product IntegrationsResourcesKnowledge CenterTutorialsReviewsWebinarsWhite PapersWho We AreAbout UsIn the NewsAwardsMagazine FeaturesPodcastsPress ReleasesOur TeamCareersBlogContactSign UpLoginPrivacy PolicyLast Revision: April 1, 2017This privacy policy applies to www.planhub.com.This version of the Privacy Policy is effective as of the date set forth above. By logging in to the system or using the website in any way, users consent to the Privacy Policy that is effective at that time. Even if users have read and approved a prior version, users agree to the version that is effective as of any date that they log in to the system or use the website.POLICY STATEMENTIn order to make our website more useful to our users, we collect personal information in a variety of ways, as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We have designed this Privacy Policy, and our underlying procedures, to best protect users’ private information while making our website as useful and user friendly as possible. We endeavor to protect our users’ private information to the greatest extent possible, but we cannot promise, and users should not expect, that personal information or private communications will always remain private.REGISTRATION OF SUBCONTRACTORS, GENERAL CONTRACTORS, HOMEOWNERS AND SUPPLIERSIn order to submit a project request or enroll as a subcontractor; a user must register with our website, including creating a unique username and password. During the registration process, a user must provide contact information. We then use this information to contact the user about services on our website for which they have expressed an interest. By submitting a project request or enrolling as a subcontractor, a user expressly consents to being contacted by us by phone, email address or mail.INFORMATION COLLECTED WHEN SUBMITTING PROJECTSA project request includes the completion of a Submit Project Form and a Personal Profile Form. The Personal Profile Form is used to register the user to our website and is only required during the first instance of a project request. At the Submit Project Form we collect information that describes the scope of the project. We will also collect information relevant to the project such as contact name, address, bid due date, email address, and relevant information about the project.INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM REGISTERED USERSUsers enroll in our service online and complete a Registration Form and agree to a Service Agreement. During the registration we may collect the following information: first and last name, company name, address, phone number, email address, membership affiliations, trades, billing address, username, password, credit card number, expiration date.HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT:The information collected is used to provide project information to qualified contractors within our network.ENHANCEMENT OF MARKETING PROFILEWe may purchase third party marketing data and add it to our user database to target our advertising and provide pertinent offers to our users. We use this information to enhance the profile of individual users, and it is tied to users’ personally identifiable information. This information is not collected directly from users, but from third party sources.USER PROFILESWe use users’ personally identifiable information to facilitate their use of our services. We create a personalized profile for each of our users by storing information we collect through a variety of mechanisms, which are explained below. This profile includes information on our users’ viewing preferences, activities on our website and interactions with PlanHub. By analyzing our users’ activities on our website and use of our services, we can improve our services and our website.DATA COLLECTIONCookies:A cookie is a very small file stored on the user’s hard drive that identifies the user to our website and assists us in data collection. We use both session cookies, which terminate when the user’s browser is closed, and persistent cookies, which must be manually deleted. Session cookies allow our system to remember information about the user only during that internet browser session. Persistent cookies allow our system to remember our users, meaning that they will not be required to log in every time that they visit our website. Users may reject these cookies, or manually delete them.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. We do, however, offer several features only available through the use of a cookie; users who have rejected our cookies may not be able to access these features.Log Files:We employ log files, which track certain information about your internet connection, including internet protocol addresses and internet service provider type. These log files are not linked to personally identifiable information of any user. By tracking this information, we are better able to analyze our users’ needs and improve our services and website.INFORMATION PLANHUB SHARESExcept as detailed in this Privacy Policy; PlanHub does not share your information with third parties. The information we collect is to facilitate our users’ use of our website and services.Aggregate Information:PlanHub collects aggregate information on our users’ use of our website, which we may share with third parties. This information does not contain personally identifiable information. Rather, this information is an anonymous summary of activities on our website.Legal Requirements:Though we strive to preserve users’ privacy, we cannot ensure that users’ private communications and other personal information will always remain confidential. For example, we may disclose personal information when required by law or when we believe parties are misusing or attempting to misuse our websites or services.Security:We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Users should also know that there is always a risk that third parties may unlawfully access private communications and information. While we use several online and offline security tools, policies and procedures, we cannot guarantee security of the information we collect or that unauthorized access will not occur.Third Parties:Users of our website are always notified when their information is being collected for marketing purposes by any outside parties, except our affiliates or service professionals.Sale, Merger or Acquisition:In the event that PlanHub goes through a merger, acquisition or asset sale, users’ personal information will likely be part of the assets transferred.LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITESThis website contains links from and to other websites that are not controlled by PlanHub. PlanHub is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. This Privacy Policy only applies to the PlanHub.com and PlanHub controlled websites. Once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.PlanHub may allow third parties to display advertisements on our site. PlanHub may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view and interact with these advertisements and connect to other sites.COMMUNICATIONS FROM PLANHUBOpt-OutUsers may always “opt-out” of having their information used for most purposes. For example, users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving those communications by replying to the e-mail or e-mailing us at support@planhub.com.Notifications for Registered UsersRegistered users of our network may receive regular communications from us regarding bid requests we have received, or directly from our users. We may use any contact information we have for our service professionals to provide such communications. Registered users can self-manage their personally identifiable information by means of logging into their secure and password-protected “Dashboards.” Changes made are immediately reflected throughout our system.Promotional CommunicationsWe send all new members an e-mail to verify usernames and passwords. Existing users will occasionally receive information on our services, products and special deals as well. We offer all users the opportunity to opt-out of these communications.NewsletterWe may provide our users with a newsletter about our services. If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and e-mail address. We also offer users the opportunity to opt-out of these types of communications.AnnouncementsWe may occasionally need to send out service-related announcements. Users may not opt-out of these communications, though they may deactivate their account entirely.NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYPlanHub may update this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice, to reflect changes in PlanHub’s practices. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will become effective upon the posting of the updated policy. You are encouraged to periodically review this Privacy Policy to inform yourself of changes to it or any of other policies. Use of this site constitutes your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy then in effect.ACCEPTANCE OF THE PRIVACY POLICYBy using this site, you accept this privacy statement. If you do not agree with this privacy statement, do not use this site. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement from time to time. Your continued use of any portion of this site, following notification or posting of such changes, will constitute your acceptance of those changes.CONTACTING PLANHUBChanges in Personal InformationUsers should e-mail Customer Support at support@planhub.com if their personal information changes or they no longer desire our services.Contact InformationIf users have any questions, concern or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@planhub.com.Corporate Headquarters(561) 656-47011665 Palm Beach Lakes Blvd #950West Palm Beach, FL 33401Additional Support Office(850) 391-90527113 Beech Ridge Trl, Ste 1Tallahassee, FL 32312GeneralHomeHow It WorksFeatures & BenefitsGeneral ContractorsSubcontractorsSuppliersSupportSearch by StateTerms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyContactResourcesWho Are WeFAQsIn The NewsCareersCopyright 2020 PlanHub. All rights reserved. | Designed by: Digital ResourceLive Chat Help
